mobilitypass.com 2018-03-05

# MobilityPass Privacy Policy | International Roaming SIM Card & Services

MobilityPass & MobilityPass.com service are provided by GlobalRoaming.com and belong this Privacy Policy.

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

GlobalRoaming has written this privacy statement to state our firm commitment to protecting our customer's privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for our web site:

GlobalRoaming, is committed to protecting our customers' privacy. We will not sell, trade or rent a customer's personal information to others. Only GlobalRoaming uses the information that is provided by our customers or gathered via our web site to communicate product, release, and or general company information.

Our order environment features several widely accepted and endorsed security methods to ensure that transactions, ordering and fulfillment are safe, and that all exchanges of information remain confidential. Your credit cards and checks are processed through separate merchant services vendors.

### The information we collect

Our web site's authorization forms require users to give us contact information (like your name, e-mail, and postal address), and demographic information (like your zip code). A Social Security Number or a company Tax Identification Number is required for tax reporting and credit checks.Our web site's authorization forms require users to give us contact information (like your name, e-mail, and postal address), and demographic information (like your zip code). A Social Security Number or a company Tax Identification Number is required for tax reporting and credit checks.

Contact information from the authorization forms is used to complete your order and to get in touch with you when necessary.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the GlobalRoaming.com and associated websites. On some pages, you can order services, make requests, and register. The type of personal information collected at these pages are:

    Name  
    Address  
    E-mail  
    Phone Number

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the type of personal information collected are the same as above.  
Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products and services. We collect visitor's contact information (their e-mail addresses) to complete orders. globalroaming.com and the vendors providing your service are the only companies retaining your information.

### The way we use information

The information that we collect from you is not shared with any other company or mailing list. When we get your information from our order forms, only a select number of people are allowed access to the data. GlobalRoaming and its vendor's customer service staff view and complete your order. All credit card information is maintained in a secure, offline, database that is not accessible over dial-up or internet links.

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order and insure you the support and availability of that service. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to activate the service and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We offer gift-cards by which you can personalize a product you order for another person. Information you provide to us to create a gift-card is only used for that purpose, and it is only disclosed to the person receiving the gift.

We use return e-mail addresses to answer e-mails we receive, this e-mail must be your override e-mail you have registered with your account for all information or instructions referring to your account. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our e-letter, account status as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

### Our commitment to Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### Our commitment to Childrens' Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18, and order our services are prohibed under 18.

### How you can access or correct your information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and is maintained by GlobalRoaming through a secured access to your management control panel. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes, we do use cookies that are strictly necessary in order to provide you the registration, shipment, the service and to maintain the security of this web site.

_This website uses also Google Analytics cookies:_

We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about the use of this website. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this website, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve this website. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the : [Google Analytics Terms of Use](http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html) et [Google Privacy Policy.](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)

You can have access to the cookies that are stored on your computer. Most browsers can be set to notify you when a cookie is stored on your computer. Most browsers can be set so that they do not accept cookies. However, this may affect your Internet experience. You can delete cookies from your computer also at any time. 

### Right to correct, block and erase the data

In accordance with EU Directive 95/46/EC, art 10, at your request, we will correct, block or erase the data stored, provided that other laws do not conflict (e.g. accounting requirements for invoices).

In order to contact us, please use the contact tab. http://www.globalroaming.com/sim/en/faq.html

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of the website.

### Your consent

By using our site, you consent to our private policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

### Important

In case of conflict about the Privacy Policy in other language, the English version is mandatory. For other language than English Global Roaming is not responsible for translation mistake or any customer damage due to a misunderstanding of the translation.

This policy was last modified on May 1, 2016
